Maybe you just got here now, but if
I'm listening to you,
今来たばかりかもだけど
話を聞いてると
you're in a space where you kind of
want to get away
問題とかドラマから
from all the problems and the drama.
離れたい時期なんだよね
But I've seen you on your streams
and stuff
でも配信とかで見てると
when you're talking about the
gambling stuff with Offset
Offsetとのギャンブルの件とか
and just different, even the Kai
Cenat stuff.
カイ・セナの件とか話してるじゃん
And it brings the drama and
the conversation
それでドラマも話題も
to you at the same time.
同時に寄ってくる
Why do you do that if you feel
like this?
そう思ってるなら
なんでそんなことすんの？
Okay, sometimes I be feeling like
so passionate,
いや、たまに熱くなっちゃうんだよ
like people gonna understand me,
みんなわかってくれるだろって
and then I be like, you know,
で、なんていうか
the team will be like, never speak,
never speak,
チームには「絶対しゃべるな」って
言われるんだけど
but I be like, but I got a point. Like,
you feel me?
「でも俺にも言い分あるし」って
なるんだよ
Like, yo... I put it like this, right? I
ain't gonna lie.
こう言わせてくれ
正直に言うと
What I thought the world was gonna
be like,
世間はこうなると思ってた
Offset, you a bum ass ni**a.
Feel me?
「Offset、お前マジで
ダセぇ奴だな」って
Because, bro... I got rappers,
だってさ、ラッパーたちとか
bro, the whole industry is in my DM.
業界中から俺のDMに来てんのよ
You see how a couple ni**as came
out? Everybody in my DM laughing.
何人か表に出てきたの見ただろ？
みんなDMで笑ってんの
Ha ha, Offset owe me bread too. The
whole world is in my DM.
「ハハ、Offsetは俺にも借りある」って
世界中からDM来てんだよ
Offset owe me bread. La la la.
Feel me?
「Offsetに金貸してる」とか
なんとかってな
So I'm like, bro, I'm over here asking
for my bread.
で、俺は金返せって言ってんのに
You keep texting me angry texts
about getting in blood.
お前は物騒なキレたメッセージ
ばっか送ってくる
I'm like, you wilding, broski. So I'm
thinking it's funny.
「お前イカれてんな」って
笑えてきてさ
Like, Offset's a bum, he over here
taking people's bread, running off.
Offsetってダセぇな
人の金持って逃げてんだもん
Hey, bro, I'll get it back in blood.
「おい、血ィ見てでも返すわ」って
I'm like, damn.
「マジかよ」って
How much did he owe you?
いくら貸してたの？
It was 10K. It was nothing, bro.
1万ドル。大した額じゃねぇよ
I threw it in the strip club whenever I
want to.
ストリップクラブで
いつでもばら撒ける額だし
That's a lot of money. That's
still 10K.
大金だろ。1万ドルは1万ドルだよ
All right, but it's not enough for me
to hate you, bro.
まぁな、でもお前を嫌いになる
ほどの額じゃねぇってこと
I just feel like you just max
disrespecting me.
ただ、めちゃくちゃ
ナメられてると思ってさ
But kudos to you, bro, for me.
でもまぁ、大したもんだよ